brocade.com 2018-11-12

# Privacy Policy | Broadcom Inc.

**Effective May 22, 2018**

Broadcom Inc. and its affiliates (“Broadcom”) value your privacy. This Privacy Statement (“Statement”) describes how Broadcom collects, stores, uses, and shares your Personal Information. This Statement is issued on behalf of Broadcom, so a reference to “we”, “us”, or “our” in this Statement is a reference to the relevant company in Broadcom that is responsible for processing your Personal Information.  

**What Information Do We Collect About You and Why?**

We may ask you to provide us with Personal Information about yourself in order to provide services to you. If you choose not to provide Personal Information that we have asked for, it may delay or prevent us from providing services to you. “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. We may collect different categories of Personal Information about you, including personal and business contact information such as name, job title, company name, contact and billing information, phone number, email address, domain name, browser type and operating system, web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; the length of time you visit our Site and/or use our services; and the URL or the webpage that led you to our Site. We may also ask you to provide information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products and contact preferences. Personal Information may be required to determine access eligibility for certain restricted parts of our Site. Personal Information about you collected on-line may be combined with information provided off-line.

**_Information We Collect Directly From You or a Third Party.  _**We collect Personal Information about when you visit our website (“Site”), register or subscribe for our services, order our products or services, create an account on our Site, request marketing or publications to be sent to you, give us feedback on our services or our Site. We also may collect Personal Information about you from third party sources, such as someone authorized by you to act on your behalf, third party services that you use that utilize or interact with our services, or where Personal Information has been provided by you at an event. We may also collect your Personal Information from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, and social media platforms.

**_Information We Collect Automatically.  _** We may automatically collect information about your use of our Site or services through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies. We may combine this information with other information that we have collected about you such as your user name. Please see our the Cookie Policy links below for more information.

  * www.broadcom.com Cookie Policy

**How Do We Use Your Information?**

We use the information collected about you for the following purposes:

  * to register you as a new customer
  * to enable you to order products or services, download software updates
  * to provide services to you
  * to allow you to make requests, and register for customized communications programs
  * to customize  the content and information that we may send or display to you to administer the careers portion of the Site and process your job application
  * for marketing and promotional purposes
  * to assist us in advertising our products and services on third party websites
  * for our business purposes to better understand how users access and use our Site, products, and services and for other research and analytical purposes, including data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Site, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities
  * to administer other programs that may be offered to customers and end users of our products and services
  * to manage our relationship with you which will include notifying you about changes to our terms or this Statement
  * as we believe necessary or appropriate, including: 
    * under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence;
    * to comply with legal process;
    * to enforce our terms and conditions;
    * to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates;
    * to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others

**With Whom Do We Share Your Information and Why?**

We do not sell, rent, or lease your Personal Information or information to others. We may share Personal Information collected about you as follows:

**_Broadcom Users.  _**Your user name and any information that you post to our Site, including, without limitation, reviews, comments, pictures and text will be available to, and searchable by, all users of the Site.

**_Affiliates or Subsidiaries._**  Information we collect from you may be shared with our affiliates or subsidiaries.

**_Unaffiliated Third Parties._**  Certain information about you may be shared with select resellers and/or distributors, particularly if you or your company have purchased through a third party before.

**_Service Providers._**  Information we collect from you may be disclosed to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf. We may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research, or similar purposes.

**_Business Transfers.   _**Information we have collected from you may be transferred to another company as part of a merger or acquisition by that company.

**How Do We Use Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms?**

Please review our Cookie Policy links below for more information about how we use cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

  * www.broadcom.com Cookie Policy

**What About Links to Other Websites?**

Our Site and services may contain links to third-party websites for your convenience. Any access to and use of such linked websites will cause you to leave the Site. Third-party websites are not governed by this Statement, but instead are governed by their own privacy statements/policies. We recommend that you check the privacy statements/policies of every third party website you visit before providing any Personal Information. We have not reviewed all of these third party websites; do not control them and are not responsible for their content or their privacy policies. Thus, we do not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party websites linked to our Site, you do so entirely at your own risk.

**How Do We Secure Your Personal Information?**

We have implemented administrative, technical, physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction and to help maintain data accuracy and ensure it your Personal Information is used appropriately. Broadcom has an internal Global Customer Privacy Program. Its charter is to ensure appropriate privacy processes are in place in order to meet the practices outlined herein. Where Personal Information is processed by service providers on behalf of Broadcom, we take steps to require those vendors to also comply with applicable data protection laws.

**Your Rights**

Depending on where you live, you may have the following rights described below with respect to your Personal Information. To exercise your rights, please send your request to [data.privacy@broadcom.com](mailto:data.privacy@broadcom.com).

**_Access_**. To request information regarding Personal Information that we hold about you and the source(s) of that information. To access your Personal Information, return to the web page where you originally entered it and follow the instructions on that web page. If you cannot access your information on the web page, please send your request to [data.](mailto:data.)[privacy@broadcom.com](mailto:data.privacy@broadcom.com).

Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Site for a period of time.

You can request a copy of any Personal Information we hold about you. This service is usually free of charge, although we have the right to charge a ‘reasonable fee’ in some circumstances;

**_Rectification._** To request that we rectify any inaccuracies in relation to the Personal Information we hold;

**_Erasure_**. In some circumstances, to request the erasure of your Personal Information or object to the processing of your information;

**_Restriction on Processing_**. In some circumstances, the right to require us to restrict processing of your Personal Information;

**_Data Portability_**. In some circumstances, to request that your Personal Information be transferred to you or a new provider if the data is processed automatically;

**_Right to Object_**. To object to any direct marketing;

**_Withdraw Consent_**. To withdraw consent to us processing your Personal Information. This will not affect the processing already carried out with your consent; and

**_Complaint_**. To lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach our supervisory authority so please contact us in the first instance.

**_Our Lead Supervisory Authority_**. We are a business that operates across a number of jurisdictions in the EU. We have therefore elected to have the Information Commissioners Office (“ICO”) in the United Kingdom as our Lead Supervisory Authority. If you wish to make a report regarding our conduct relating to your Personal Information, please contact the ICO at <https://ico.org.uk/concerns/>. 

**What Choices Do You Have Regarding Use of Your Personal Information?**

We will not use or share your Personal Information in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first notifying you and offering a choice, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. Please note that we may process your Personal Information without your knowledge or consent where it is required or permitted by law.

We will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you wish to opt-out at any time of certain or all contact from us, and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. This choice will be offered at the bottom of our on-line or off-line communications to you as well as on many of our web registration pages. If you have any difficulty exercising your choices, please send your request to [data.privacy@broadcom.com](mailto:data.privacy@broadcom.com).

Your permission will always be secured first, should we ever decide to share your Personal Information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy statement.

**How Can You Contact Us?**

We have appointed a Data Protection Officer who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. If you have questions or concerns about this Statement, or the privacy practices relating to our Site or services or wish to contact our Data Protection Officer, please contact us using the details below:

Company name: Broadcom Inc.

Email address: [data.privacy@broadcom.com](mailto:data.privacy@broadcom.com)

Postal address: 1320 Ridder Park Drive, San Jose, CA 95131

**How Long Do We Retain Your Personal Information?**

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Statement unless a longer retention period is required by law.

**What about Children?**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information relating to children. If you believe that we may have collected Personal Information from someone under the age of thirteen (13), or under the applicable age of consent in your country, without parental consent, please let us know using the methods described in the Contact Us section and we will take appropriate measures to investigate and address the issue promptly.

**What about California Privacy Rights?**

California law, under California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (known as the "Shine the Light" law), permits our established customers who are California residents to request information regarding the manner in which shares certain categories of your Personal Information with third parties, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to Broadcom at its designated address and receive the following information:

1\.   The categories of information Broadcom disclosed to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year;

2\.   The names and addresses of third parties that received such information; and

3\.   If the nature of a third party's business cannot be reasonably determined from the third party's name, examples of the products or services marketed.

You are entitled to receive a copy of this information up to one request per calendar year in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you individually. Broadcom’s designated email address for such requests is [data.privacy@broadcom.com](mailto:data.privacy@broadcom.com). We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted to addresses other than the addresses specified in this paragraph. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response.  Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.

**How Are Transfers of Data Performed?**

Subject to your permission or as permitted by law, the Personal Information that you provide to us may be transferred within Broadcom across state or country borders. This may be done to consolidate data storage or to simplify the management of customer information. We have adopted globally recognized privacy principles and only collect and/or share your Personal Information to the extent it is necessary to conduct business and perform requested services. Broadcom in the United States and service providers comply with applicable legal requirements providing for adequate protection of Personal Information transferred to countries outside of the EEA and Switzerland.

**What about Changes to this Privacy Statement?**

This Privacy Statement is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Statement from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Statement on our Site. If we make any changes to this Statement that materially affect our practices with regard to the Personal Information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavour to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site, or by sending you an e-mail message to the e-mail address you have provided.
